come on, there is no
давай так в Брянской области нету
nuclear power plant in the Bryansk region, if Ukraine takes over the
атомной станции если Украина захватит
entire Bryansk region, will it be a threat to the
всю брянскую область это будет угроза
integrity of the country or not,
целостности страны или нет
and Putin actually said that there are
а Путин вообще сказал что в Брянской
only people living in the Bryansk region, otherwise the Bryansk region
области живут одни а то брянскую область
can be given to Ukraine. Yes, that’s why
можно отдавать Украине Да поэтому походу
I’m from the city of Khmelnitsky.
да я из города Хмельницкий Вы
Where are you from? I’m from  in Samara you
откуда Я из самарой
talk about the World Cup, but
о ЧМ общаетесь
basically about nothing, just
ту да по сути ни о чём
what else to do in Russia, it’s boring, they
просто А что ещё делать в России скучно
pay salaries just like that, so you don’t have to work, as
платят поэтому можно и не работать как
it were, and pensions, too,
бы и пенсии тоже
nothing on the sly Well,
ничего потихонечку
at the same time, we send missiles
Ну заодно это ракеты отправляем
to the
на
front, but there is a
фронт но есть
nuance, the missiles are sent under their own power
нюанс ракеты своим ходом
Samara region,
отправляются с Самарской области в том
including Well, I’m listening to tell you So what to
числе Ну рассказывать я слушаю Так а что
tell? Everything is interesting,
рассказывать Всё интересно
I heard there that they also fly there under their own power,
я я там слышал что там ещё своим ходом
and in the Samara region
прилетают и в самарскую область
in Sarato in Mata there was a case in general By the way,
в сарато в Мэта было дело вообще Кстати
it flew in from Kazakhstan,
это прилетела вообще из Казахстана
it doesn’t matter to me where it
это мне вообще без разницы откуда она
came from  the main thing is that it arrived
прилетела главное что прилетела
in general. Well, it doesn’t matter, we didn’t find out
вообще А ну без разницы не мы узнали
where it came from and what I’m doing, how and
откуда прилетела и что как и
what, well, it’s difficult. Well, now it means that with
что делаю ну сложно Ну вот теперь Значит
small ones they will, in short, bomb
мелкими нами и будут короче бомбить
you bomb residential buildings yes Seriously And what
вас бомбить жилые дома да Серьёзно И что
will you do and what will you
вы сделаете и что вы
do Well, Ukraine is the same  a
сделаете Ну Украина - это же государство
terrorist state, it will bomb your residential
террорист оно будет бомбить ваши жилые
buildings through Kazakhstan And that you will do
дома через Казахстан И что вы сделаете
nothing Well, this is a normal statement, yes,
ничего Ну нормальное такое заявление да
but what, by the right of the strong, we are bombing
а что вот мы по праву сильного бомбим
your residential buildings and what will you do?
ваши жилые дома и что вы сделаете Так вы
he’s such an organization Well, yes, that’s all Well,
он тако организация Ну да вот и всё Ну
if there’s nowhere to turn, be patient, we
вот если некуда обращаться терпите вы мы
’ll bomb,
будем бомбить е
so what? And if a nuclear weapon arrives and doesn’t arrive,
что А если ядерка прилетит а не прилетит
we thought, look, it’s clear when the
Мы думали смотри уже ж Понятно когда
Kursk region was occupied, and then you
курскую область оккупировали да то уже и
won’t even arrive anymore. First, we thought there
не прилете уже все Сначала думали
would be a Crimean bridge  nuclear then
Крымский мост будет ядерка потом
they shelled Belgorod there will be a nuclear and
обстреливали Белгород будет ядерка а
now when they stupidly went they stupidly went
теперь когда уже тупо зашли зашли тупо
into the Kursk region already 2 months
короче в курскую область уже 2 месяца
in 2 days there will be 2 months of the Kurdish
через 2 дня будет 2 месяца курдского
movement and that’s it What kind of nuclear dude, forget
движа и всё Какая ядерка чувак забудь у
it, damn it at the airfield in Plesetsk On
вас он блин на аэродроме в Плесецке На
tests with a rocket right in the silo  when you
испытаниях с ракета прям в шахте при
leave the Shah
выходе Шах
training ground, you're already
полигон с вас уже все
laughing
жу гонов
a few times, you're laughing, everything's not
несколько всё так с вас ржут всё никакой
bright at all We're really showing the whole
ярки всё Мы реально показываем всему
world Yes, you can bomb your residential
миру Да что можно бомбить ваши жилые
buildings, you can, in short, damn it, capture your
дома можно короче блин захватывать вашу
area And you won't do anything, no
область И вы ничего не сделаете никакого
cannonballs, yoke, be proud of it, be proud of it Yes
ядер иго этим гордись гордимся Да
proud
горжусь
proud Yeah Funny
гордимся Угу Забавно
Yes, the simple fact is that it’s literally
Да просто дело в том что буквально
nice when NATO can shoot up
приятно когда НАТО может расстреливать
high-rise buildings simply with impunity in Russia
многоэтажки просто безнаказанно в России
Well, so what and what will you do NATO nothing?
Ну и что и что вы сделаете НАТО ничего А
Yes, it’s really cool that a few
да вот именно прикольно что несколько
days ago the nuclear
дней назад буквально изменилась ядерная
doctrine of Russia literally changed not a few days ago
доктрина России не несколько дней назад
but a month  at
а месяц как
least it was on the eighteenth there Well, yes,
минимум это было восемнадцатого там А ну
although no, that I won’t be here for two weeks already
да хотя нет что я вона это уже недели
Well, two weeks ago Yes, that is, not
две Ну недели две Да назад то есть не
yesterday, really Well,
вчера правда
yes, you understand a little in Russia that what is the
да немножко понимаешь в России что что
nuclear doctrine, what did they say about the nuclear
ядерная доктрина что там сказали ядерной
doctrine, they allowed
доктрине там разрешили
strikes on other territories if  these
удары по другим территориям если эти
territories
территории
are using the help of other countries, yes,
пользуются помощью других стран да так
look, in your nuclear
смотрите у вас и раньше в ядерной
doctrine, it was possible to use a nuclear weapon in an attack on Russia before,
доктрине при нападении на Россию можно
true, true,
было использовать ядерку правда верно
no, not true, no, look, it was not
нет не так нет Смотри не там было
allowed to use a nuclear weapon only
разрешено использовать ядерку только
if it threatens the integrity of the country. Yes, an
если это угрожает целостности страны Да
attack threatens an attack on the Kursk region
нападение нападение на курскую область
integrity of the country No why,
угрожает целостности страны Нет почему
because not if they took away from you the
так как не если у вас забрали у вас
country is no longer a whole; part of the region was taken away from it as a
страна уже не целая от неё забрали часть
whole, don’t wait, not Russia,
области целостно не подожди не Россия
it’s such a big country,
она страна такая большая
that is, the integrity of the
то есть целостность
country consists of several
страны заключается из нескольких
factors, that is, yes, you can call there,
факторов то есть да ты можешь там в
I just think  yes, that is, I
звать я просто думаю да то есть я
understood correctly Look, if
правильно понял Смотри если от страны
part of the territory is taken away from the country Yes, the integrity of
забрать часть территории Да целостность
the country will not be violated Yes if it is not
не будет нарушена страны Да если она не
unimportant on a strategic scale then yes
неважная стратегическом масштабе то да
no
нено
Nano if we unscrew its
Нано если мы у него открутить
headlight is it a whole car or no yes yes is
фару это целый автомобиль или нет да да
it a whole car understood yes If we
это целый автомобиль понял да Если мы у
Break off a small one from the vase, it will be a whole
вазы отломать маленький это будет целая
vase,
ваза
but this is up to the owner of the vase,
м а вот это вот уже от хозяина ваза
well the question is: If the entire Kursk
зависит хорошо вопрос Если всю курскую
region is taken away, will it be the whole of
область заберут это будет ещё целая
Russia or
Россия или
not there is a nuclear power plant there, of course
нет там АЭС конечно
it won’t be there anymore I don’t understand again, of
это уже не будет Не понял ещё раз
course Well,
конечно Ну
first of all, if so  already now Yesterday,
во-первых если как уже сейчас Вчера
in my opinion, they were fired at
по-моему были обстреляли Да обстреляли
Yes, they fired at the nuclear power plant Yes, we fired at the nuclear power plant,
АС Да мы обстреляли
but if there is
АС вот если будет
damage to the station, then Yes,
ущерб станции то Да
that is, this will already be a threat to the
это то есть это уже будет угроза
integrity of the country Yes, yes, yes, I understood
целостности страны Да да да так понял
well, and then and then Russia has the
хорошо и тогда и тогда Россия имеет
right again,
право опять
okay And if if Ukraine  will not
хорошо А если если Украина не будет
take over the nuclear power plant Yes, but it
захватывать атомную станцию Да но
will take over the entire Kursk region without the nuclear
захватит всю курскую область без атомной
power plant and the Belgorod region, will it be a
станции и Белгородской область это будет
threat to the integrity of the country or not So
угроза целостности страны или нет Так
this is
это
impossible Well, it’s trivial because the
невозможно Ну банально потому что
nuclear power plant is infrastructure
атомная станция - это инфраструктура
Okay, look, there is the Kursk region
Ладно смотрите вот есть Курская область
Yes, Ukraine will leave a piece of
Да вот Украина так обог кусочек оставит
Kursk  region from the nuclear power plant Yes, but the
Курской области с атомной станции Да а
rest of the Kursk region will be captured by the
остальную часть Курской области захватит
integrity of the country or is it not so,
это уже целостность строны или не так
it’s impossible, I
это невозможно я
repeat, you need to be transported to the nuclear power plant
повторяюсь на атомную станцию нужно
there Well, yes, we are from the
подвозить там Ну так да мы со стороны
Lipetsk region We will leave the road to the
Липецкой области Мы оставим дорогу на
nuclear power plant from the Lipetsk
атомную станцию со стороны Липецкой
region, that is, there will be transport  so there
области то есть будет подвоз так там
will be military equipment there too, then there won’t
будет и военная техника тогда заходить
be no entry. They’ll put shorter
не не не будет Вот там поставят короче
cordons there, like they’ll make 20 km
типа кордоны типа типа сделают 20 км
around the station, delirium zono, they won’t go
вокруг станции делирий зоно ти не бут
there,
туда
the rest of the Armed Forces. Oh, you understand the
оста ВС О ты понимаешь
nonsense. Okay, look, let’s say,
бред Хорошо смотри давай так в Брянской
there is no nuclear power plant in the Bryansk region if
области нету атомной станции если
Ukraine takes over  the entire Bryansk region will
Украина захватит всю брянскую область
it be a threat to the integrity of the country or
это будет угроза целостности страны или
not? Putin actually said that in the Bryansk
нет Путин вообще сказал что в Брянской
region there are
области живут
only people living in the Bryansk region. The Bryansk region can be given to
одни брянскую область можно отдавать
Ukraine. Yes, that’s why the campaign
Украине Да поэтому походу да
like it this way. The Bryansk region,
нравится так Брянская область
prepare now you’ve already been handed over like that, and the
приготовите сейчас вас уже сдали так а
Belgorod
Белгородская
region, the Belgorod region. Well, a campaign
область Белгородской области Ну походу
like that, probably Well, partially  too, that
типа того наверное Ну частично тоже то
is, Belgorodskaya can also be taken away and there
есть Белгородскую тоже можно забирать и
will be no nuclei,
ядер не будет
no, you can’t sing a whole piece as
да нет целиком нельзя кусочек поть
long as it’s good. Can you
покуда хорошо по А можете огласите
please announce the entire list of regions and their
пожалуйста весь список областей и их
parts that can be taken away, but I don’t, I do
частей которые можно забрать бе я я не я
n’t know, you understand what’s wrong, I understand the
не знаю понимаешь В чём дело-то понял
Rostov region well  part if
хорошо Ростовскую область часть если
we take it will be a nuclear weapon or not not from
заберём будет ядерка или нет не с
Rostov in general there everything is understood everything from
Ростовской вообще там всё всё понял всё
Rostov we don’t go like that Voronezh
ростовскую не лезем так Воронежская
region
область
part of Voronezh Well we ourselves bomb it
часть Воронеж Ну мы сами бомбим его
periodically that’s what we understood
периодически этому что уж там понял
Voronezh we’re taking it so uh Krasnodar
Воронеж забираем так э Краснодарский
Voronezh
Воронеж
if it’s not there you’re what is it  the breadbasket of
как не это там ты что это это же житница
Russia is that I understood everything. So, in short, we
России это что всё понял Значит короче
take away the Bryansk one. In general, we understand the Bryansk one,
брянскую забираем В общем понял брянскую
we take away all the Kursk partly
забираем полностью курскую частично
the Belgorod one, we leave a small piece for
Белгородскую оставляем маленький кусочек
you from the Voronezh one, we take the Rostov one and
вам воронежскую забираем ростовскую и
Krasnodar one, we don’t touch the normal scheme,
Краснодар не трогаем нормальная схема
I liked it. So
мне понравилась Вот и Донбасс э с
we give Donbass and Lugansk, that’s the normal one, those Ukraine ones are
Луганском отдаём вот нормальная те украи
not what Ukraine.  You said
не какой Украине Ты что Вы же сказали
we’ll give it back, well we’ll give it back to us, we’ll give it to you No one will
отдаём ну отдаём нам отдаём вам Никто не
give anything back,
отдаст ничего
not like this Crimea was given away already here, not for
не как это Крым отдали уже тут уже не за
Crimea, they haven’t
Крым ещё не воевали
even fought yet, they haven’t even started yet, they just
даже вот даже ещё и не начинали просто
fired on it,
обстреливали
but why good? And the question is, will you
да А зачем хоро А вопрос а Владивосток
give Vladivostok to
отдадите
Ukraine? Vladivostok to
Украине Владивосток
Ukraine and Ukraine  - What is this? It’s like a
Украине а Украина - Это что Это как
country. Like, it can get to
страна Типа она может добраться до
Vladivostok, it doesn’t matter. We’ll rent it out to
Владивостока неважно Мы в аренду
the Chinese,
китайцам
they’ll get there. How do they sign
сдадим они доберутся Каким
on the papers? So the Chinese
образом на бумаг подпи так китайцы
will be against it. I mean, on the contrary, the Chinese
против будут В смысле наоборот китайцы
will only rent from us for
только за в аренду возьмут у нас на
1488, they don’t have it, and so they already have Vladivostok
1488 нет у них и так есть Владивосток
almost no property so
уже почти в собственности нет поэтому
they want to legally formalize
они хотят юридически оформить
it through Ukraine
это через Украину
Yes, they need an
Да нужен
intermediary, they need an intermediary, yes, I have
посредник посредником нужен да что-то я
n’t heard anything like that from the Chinese, in short,
такого от китайцев не слышал то короче
let’s now go back to the doctrine, tell me,
давай теперь вернёмся к доктрине скажи
you said that they adopted an update
ты сказал что вот там приняли обновление
to the doctrine, what did they
в доктрину что там
accept? When can you strike?  from the main thing
приняли Когда можно ударить из основного
this is that if the intermediary country
это то что если страна посредник будет
attacks the territory of
нападать на территорию
Russia with the help of the intermediary’s weapons. Well, in
России с помощью оружия посредника Ну в
the sense, with the help of the
смыс с помощью оружия
original weapons. So Russia can
первоначального Вот то Россия может
hit the country, both the intermediary and the
ударить по стране Как посреднику так и
original one, that is, conditionally, if
первоначальному то есть условно если
there were missiles and other things, I mean,
ракеты что там шел и прочие Поня су
look Yes  Kurchatov Kurchatov Where is the
смотрите Да Курчатов Курчатов Где стоит
ES fired at the highmore themselves yesterday or the pose
Эс обстреляли хаймор сами вчера или поза
yesterday with American weapons How have you
вчера американским оружием Как вы
reacted in any way so far because there
отреагировали пока никак потому что
was no damage That is, I understand correctly that it is
было То есть я правильно понимаю что
possible to simply fire at Russian territory with American weapons,
территорию России можно
yes Russia can
да Россия может
make such a decision But I didn’t
принять такое решение Но это не
necessarily understand
обязательно понял
this  that we have a red
в том что у нас красное
line, I’m a
линии я
glitch, your whole T-shirt is
сбой у тебя вся футболка
red from the red
Красная от красных
lines Well, that’s it,
линий Ну вот так вот да
well, it’s not worth laughing because it’s
хорошо ржать не стоит потому что ржать
not worth laughing because
не стоит потому что
it’s possible World War III Already
это это возможно Третья Мировая Уже
what does nuclear have to do with it,
причём ядерная
damn it This isn’t
это блин Это не
funny I don’t know why they’re laughing Why
смешно Я не знаю почему смеются Почему
So you laugh,
Вот вы смеётесь
it’s
это
all at once that there will be no Moscow Well, there won’t
всем сразу то что Москвы не будет Ну не
be Moscow and everything super goal has been achieved
будет Москвы и всё супер цель достигнута
and you won’t be like that either And what’s
так и вас тоже не будет так А что
important is that there should be no Moscow, that’s the goal
главное чтобы Москвы не было вот э цель
God created the Ukrainians To destroy
Бог создал украинцев Чтобы уничтожить
Moscow
Москву
through the Austrian
через австрийский
General Staff the statement is simply strong
генштаб заявление просто сильное очень
Ukraine’s very mission is to destroy
миссия Украины - это в уничтожение
Moscow. This is because Moscow is the
Москвы Это потому что Москва - это есть
devil incarnate. Yes, and the Ukrainians are
воплощение дьявола Да а украинцы - это
God’s angelic army. Yes, we
ангельское Божье войско Да мы
should pump it up with propaganda. Yes,
должны накачали пропагандой да
the question is. Well, where? At the moment, we
вопрос Ну где На данный момент у нас
have red lines there in
проходят красные линии там по
Russia. No, after such statements.
России Нет после таких заявлений
Sorry.  I'm
Извините я
a smoke break
Перекур
What is this
Что это
somehow This somehow smacks of
как-то Это как-то попахивает
some kind of propaganda
например пропагандой какой-то
Well like For example
Ну как Например
you yourself said Repeat these
вы сами заявили Повторите эти
words strange
слова странный
man strange You are a
человек странный Вы
man where now I repeat where
человек где сейчас я повторяю где сейчас
Russia is now passing beautifully is it good before the
проходят России крас ли хорошо пред
last
послед
words I won’t think the last  or the
слова я не буду думать последний или
penultimate one
предпоследний
about
про то
where because of what the
где из-за Чего
Ukrainians were invented there and so on
украинцы были придуманы там и так далее
And yes God invented created the Ukrainians to
А да Бог придумал создал украинцев для
destroy
уничтожения
Moscow
Москвы
Uh-huh This is important yes all the best
Угу Это важно да всего доброго до
goodbye And God cannot be wrong with us
свидания А Бог не может ошибаться з нами
God Glory to Ukraine write to my Telegram
бог Слава украини пись на мий Telegram
right now  VN and so much
прям зараз ось ВН а
more and more respectfully YouTube has taken
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg ORV in your ban and even more
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
video I don’t show people at all times I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we can write an operational link in Mali
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
right away and while there in
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
okm the video is also the same Tsikava  and korisna
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and mi povinni z you trimati
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
lenten operational connection
постный оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe a
подпишись а